# Andrew Kohn

# A Determined & Passionate Software Developer

Minnetonka, MN 55343 contact@kohnandrew.com (952)-649-0759

I have a rich 9-year background in healthcare where I worked multiple roles to ensure success in a team environment:

- Technical Support: Ensure all technical hardware, software, and devices are operational and running smoothly.
- Administration: Work closely with RN's, LPN's, and admins to help fulfill needs such as creating & editing documents and/or policies, billing & payroll, and staff/patient scheduling.
- Certified Nursing Assistant: I assist and care for vulnerable adults with physical, psychological, and behavioral issues.
- Maintenance: Troubleshoot, maintain, and fix problems with HVAC, electrical, or any appliance issues.

I try to implement coding when applicable to help complete tasks more efficiently and to be less prone to errors. Feel free to browse my projects on GitHub:

https://github.com/AndrewKohn

Notable completed projects use in work tasks:

- https://github.com/AndrewKohn/PayrollReportSorter [Java]
- https://github.com/AndrewKohn/PDFWordConverter [Java]
- https://github.com/AndrewKohn/MGH-menu [HTML/CSS, JavaScript]

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

### IT Support / Admin

Morning Glory Homes - Minnetonka, MN August 2013 to Present

- Assist in troubleshooting our patient's electronics, like televisions, laptops, phones, and software.
- Assist staff and patients with informing them of a device's features and uses in a way that it is clear and easy to understand.
- Technical troubleshooting to keep devices fully operational so our staff can utilize a vital online hospital charting software.
- Identify and resolve issues regarding broken medical electronic devices (i.e., determining if the device has an issue with its power supply or perhaps there was a faulty hardware that made it unresponsive).
- Built all Windows PC's for use by admins and RN's. Acquired and set up all laptops for use by CNA's/RN's in our homes.
- Attended to any modem/router issues and resolved connectivity problems swiftly between all facilities.
- Installation and maintenance of hardware and software as well as ensuring devices and drivers are updated.
- Set up of VPN on the facility's devices.

- Set up of remote desktop for all vital admin/RN desktops.
- Acquired, installed, and maintained all laser/inkjet printers for all facilities, which also allowed for easier day-to-day productivity with the features of wireless/airprint printing and e-fax capabilities.
- Maintained a clean work area and kept good cable-management habits across the offices and areas CNA's/RN's use frequently.
- Assist in creating and providing documents for use by admins, RN's (Registered Nurses), CNA's (Certified Nursing Assistants), doctors, social workers, and to our residents and/or their family members/ quardians.
- Assisted in billing for residents' insurances and taxes for residents.
- Assisted in providing support for RN's and admins regarding our online charting service or our online staffing software that assists all our staff with their paystubs, benefits, scheduling, etc...
- Cross-trained from a CNA position, and would often help fill in scheduling issues, since our facilities provides care 24/7.
- Socialized with patients and offered help or defused disputes.
- Transports patients to-and-from medical facilities and/or their personal needs (i.e. going to the store.).
- Misc. tasks (repair, electrical, plumbing) and construction project tasks (constructing new rooms to code, ensuring structural safety for staff and patients, handicap accessibility.). Allowed for adapting to new issues and executing actions to solve problems the correct way.

### **Sales Associate/Customer Service**

Office Max - Chanhassen, MN August 2011 to August 2013

- One of the first points of contact with customers entering the store or phoning in.
- Guided customers to laptops, computers, printers, and other electronic devices that fit their needs.
- Cross-trained in computer repair and troubleshooting computer security issues.
- Knowledge on computer hardware assisted in guiding customers to their products.
- Knowledge on laser/inkjet printers helped assist customers regarding efficiencies regarding printer usage. This was very useful to pinpoint customer's needs, especially if their needs are business related and cost of printing are an actual factor. Knowledge on these systems and their functions can deeply help the customer's rate of return on the products purchased.
- Cross-trained in printing services, which was a high-traffic service at the time.
- Inspect returns for repackaging or sending RMA's out of the facility.

# Education

### Associate in Science (AS) in Computer Science

Normandale Community College - Bloomington, MN September 2020 to Present

#### High school diploma

Minnetonka Senior High School - Minnetonka, MN September 2004 to June 2008

#### Skills

- Computer Hardware (9 years)
- Software Troubleshooting (10+ years)

- Microsoft Windows (10+ years)
- Operating Systems (9 years)
- Technical Support (9 years)
- Java (1 year)
- Microsoft Office (9 years)
- C/C++ (1 year)
- HTML5 (1 year)
- CSS (1 year)
- JavaScript (1 year)
- React (Less than 1 year)
- Python (Less than 1 year)
- Git (1 year)
- GitHub (1 year)
- Computer Science (1 year)
- Software Development (1 year)

#### Links

https://github.com/AndrewKohn

# Certifications and Licenses

### **Certified Food Safety Manager**

February 2019 to February 2024

### **Licensed Assisted Living Director**

Currently in training.

#### Assessments

# **Data Entry: Accuracy — Expert**

August 2020

Entering data quickly and accurately

Full results: Expert

# Working with MS Word Documents — Expert

August 2020

Knowledge of various Microsoft Word features, functions, and techniques.

Full results: Expert

### **Customer Focus & Orientation — Highly Proficient**

August 2020

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity

Full results: Highly Proficient

# Creating Presentations with Microsoft PowerPoint — Proficient

August 2020

Knowledge of Microsoft PowerPoint tools and features.

Full results: Proficient

# Typing — Expert

August 2020

Transcribing text using a standard keyboard

Full results: Expert

# **Basic Computer Skills: PC — Expert**

August 2020

Performing basic computer operations, navigating a Windows OS, and troubleshooting common computer problems.

Full results: Expert

### **Social Media — Proficient**

August 2020

Creating content, communicating online, and building a brand's reputation.

Full results: Proficient

### **Active Listening — Highly Proficient**

December 2020

Actively listening and appropriately responding in conversations

Full results: Highly Proficient

# **Work Style: Conscientiousness — Highly Proficient**

November 2020

Tendency to be well-organized, rule-abiding, and hard-working

Full results: Highly Proficient

# Following Directions — Expert

December 2020

Following multi-step instructions

Full results: Expert

# **Verbal Communication — Highly Proficient**

December 2020

Speaking clearly, correctly, and concisely

Full results: Highly Proficient

### **Technical support — Proficient**

June 2022

Performing software, hardware, and network operations

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued
development in any professional field.